# 大家好 我是王刚
Hello, everyone, I’m Wang Gang
# 本期视频我给大家分享一道甜品
For this episode, I’m sharing a recipe for dessert with you.
# 炸鲜奶
Deep-fried milk
# 首先我们准备纯牛奶250克倒入碗中
Firstly, we need to pour 250 grams of milk into the bowl.
# 不喜欢纯牛奶的同学可以用酸奶代替
You can use yogurt instead of milk if you prefer.
# 然后加入玉米淀粉30克搅拌均匀备用
Secondly, add 30 grams of corn starch and fully whisk it up with milk.
# 中途加入白糖30克
Add 30 grams of sugar during the mixing.
# 不喜欢甜味的同学可以不加
You don’t have to add sugar if you prefer a lighter taste.
# 准备模具一个均匀地刷上食用油备用
Oil spray the cake mold.
# 刷油的目的是防止牛奶粘连
The propose of it is to prevent the milk from sticking on it
# 下一步开始准备煮奶
Next, we need to prepare to boil the milk.
# 首先我们把锅洗干净
Get a clean wok
# 锅中最好不要有残留的油
With no grease left on it.
# 牛奶下锅之后先开中火烧开
Pour our milk into the wok and heat it up after.
# 然后转小火边煮边搅拌以防止糊锅
Stir it while simmering on low heat.
# 煮的过程中必须随时观察牛奶稠度的变化
Always observe changes in milk consistency while simmering it.
# 一旦牛奶变成粘稠性质之后即可关火出锅
Once the milk became gooey, we can turn the heat off.
# 然后将牛奶糊倒入刷满油的模具中
Pour the milk into the oil sprayed mold.
# 同学们也可以用比较浅的盘子
or a shallow pan.
# 然后将其放入冰箱中冷藏一个小时
Put it in the refrigerator for an hour.
# 冷藏1小时之后将凝固的牛奶（糊）取出
Pull out the frozen milk after an hour in the refrigerator.
# 然后切成大小均匀的条
Slice it into strips.
# 切好之后放入碗中下一步开始准备挂糊
Next, prepare for the battering
# 准备适量的面包糠倒入碗中（约50克）
Get 50 grams of breadcrumbs
# 然后将切好的奶糊均匀的粘上一层面包糠
Dip the milk strips into the breadcrumbs
# 粘好面包糠之后取出备用
until well combined.
# 准备鸡蛋2个打入碗中搅拌均匀备用
Whisk 2 eggs in a bowl.
# 鸡蛋打散之后加入奶糊滚一遍
Dip the milk strips into the egg mixture.
# 然后再粘上一层面包糠
dip the milk into the breadcrumbs for the second time.
# 这样的目的是将奶糊充分的粘上辅料
The propose of it is making sure the milk strips are fully coated with breadcrumbs.
# 均匀的裹好原材料之后下一步开始制作
Now, we can move to the next phase.
# 首先我们把锅烧热
Heat up the wok
# 锅烧热之后加入小宽油
Pour Kuan You (literally “broad oil”) into the wok
# 油温5成热之后将奶糊依次下入锅中
Heat up the oil to 150°C and deep-fry the milk strips
# 然后转中小火炸1分钟
Turn the heat to medium-low for 1 minute.
# 这一步的目的是将奶糊炸至表面金黄酥脆
Until it is crunchy and golden-brown
# 同学们切记不能开大火否则容易炸糊
Please remember to keep the heat low to prevent burning.
# 炸至1分钟之后即可出锅装盘
It will be ready after 1 minute of deep-frying
# 一道外酥里嫩的炸鲜奶就制作完成
We’ve completed preparing a dish with crunchy paste and milky stuff, deep-fried milk.
# 下面开始技术总结
Now, Let’s summarize the key techniques
# 第一，牛奶可以根据自己的喜好选择不同的口味
Firstly, you can choose all kinds of flavors of milk according to your preference.
# 第二，煮牛奶的时候必须小火慢煮，这样才能够均匀的受热
Secondly, When simmering the milk, you must simmer it on low heat so that you can heat the milk evenly.
# 第三，奶糊下锅之前油温不能过高或者过低，最好将其保持在5成热，否则容易炸糊或者不够酥脆
You must keep the oil at 150°C to making sure the milk strips are crunchy as we expect.
# 炸鲜奶的技术总结完毕
Above are all techniques for deep-fried milk.